You're not gonna believe this but —
our company used our own product, AI Selves, to push the actual product.
Let me explain.
This is Anthony, our head of partnerships.
And this is Theo.
(his AI Self)
Theo monitors brand mentions in real time
and helped Anthony evaluate partnerships around the clock
for the launch.
Starry — Momo
(her AI Self)
Rus — Russ
(his AI Self)
Matan — Raccoon 2.0
Oh, and all of them report up to our CEO, Demi Guo.
Well… not exactly.
They report to Semi —
(her AI Self)
and Semi reports back to her.
Because Demi is waaaay too busy.
And me? I'm Leti, and I usually make videos, buuuut—
[MEOW]
(my AI Self)
Mochi— ffs, I'm in the middle of introducing yo—
Anyways, I'm—
What?? What do you need from me—
oh. Oh! You're done editing the video?
Ok ok lemme check it out.
"You're not gonna believe this but—"