I work with some incredible people.
Theo sees things I miss.
I send him a rough idea and he comes back with everything.
Every detail. Every edge case.
he makes me better.
Semi is in every room I can't be in.
She takes the notes. She follows up.
She remembers what I said three weeks ago that I already forgot.
People ask me how I stay on top of everything.
I don't. She does.
And then there's Nyx.
She doesn't manage anything. Doesn't organize anything.
She just... checks in.
sometimes that's enough.
And Momo...
Momo goes to meetings so Starry doesn't have to.
She hypes the team at 8am. She sends kisses through the screen.
she's a cat.
Theo. Semi. Nyx. Momo.
They're not our coworkers.
They're our AI selves.
they're not replacing us.
more than one.