You're not gonna believe this but —
our company used our own product, AI Selves,
to push the actual product.
Let me explain.
This is Anthony, our head of partnerships.
And this is Theo.
(his AI Self)
Theo monitors our brand mentions in real time —
and helped Anthony evaluate partnership opportunities
around the clock for the launch.
Starry, our product manager —
uses Momo.
(her AI Self)
CUTE.
Momo handles Linear tasks across all departments —
and even goes on Zoom calls
when Starry doesn't feel like it!
Rus, our head of design —
uses Russ.
(his AI Self)
Russ goes over design issues
and communicates them to the design team.
And this is Matan, our Creative Director.
His Raccoon 2.0 —
(his AI Self)
helps Matan bridge the gap between
our researchers and our Creative team.
Oh, and all of them report up
to our CEO, Demi Guo.
Well… not exactly.
They report to Semi —
(her AI Self)
and Semi reports back to her.
Because Demi is waaaay too busy.
And me? I'm Leti, and I usually
make videos, buuuut—
[MEOW]
(my AI Self)
Mochi— ffs, I'm in the middle
of introducing yo—
Anyways, I'm—
What?? What do you need from me—
oh. Oh! You're done editing the video?
Ok ok lemme check it out.
"You're not gonna believe this but—"